庆新春过大年
Chinese new year
我们现在看到的是
is now celebrated throughout the world,
英国伦敦
特拉法尔加广场即将举行的
and we're about to witness
春节嘉年华巡游活动
a spring festival carnival parade
这里处处洋溢着浓浓的节日气氛
Here...
现如今已经在世界各地渐成风气
He's finally slithered out of his cave.
马上行动
Bold move for a coward.
就等你了
Where have you been?
真磨叽
You're late!
新年快乐
Happy new year!
过年好
什么呀?
What are these?
礼物啊
Presents!
大过年就买这么点东西
Showing up late with just these?
你好意思进去吗?
You've got some nerve!
还有呢
There are more.
不行了  我拿不了了
Wait, I can't manage.
哪个是我的?
Where's mine?
就我踢的这个
The one I just juggled.
踢坏我可不要啊
If it's smashed, keep it.
那我帮你拿着
I'll put it in storage.
走你
Get in!
来啦
We're here!
来快帮我拿一下
Give me a hand.
小宇来啦  叔叔
- Here's lei! - Uncle,
新年快乐  身体健康  万事如意
- I wish you the best of luck and health.
谢谢
- Thank you so much!
好多礼物啊
So many presents!
嘉华  干爹抱抱
Jiahua!
这位呢
This young man
就是我女婿的同事
works with my son-in-law.
他工作非常的优秀
He's super capable
人呢  也很老实的
and a decent man, too.
主要呀
Moreover,
他还单身
he is unattached!
亲一个
A smooch...
跟干爹亲一个
Give godfather a kiss!
女儿来电话
A call from my daughter!
喂  爸
Hi, dad!
新年快乐  身体健康
Happy new year!
恭喜发财  新年快乐
Happy new year to you, too.
你的咽炎好点了没有啊?
How's your sore throat?
没犯
I'm good.
听女儿的话
I heeded your advice,
烟早就戒了
and quit smoking.
你在哪儿呢?
Where are you?
我现在在非洲
I'm in Africa!
给你看
Let me show you...
你在非洲?
Africa?
看到了吗?
Can you see?
那些地方要小心点啊
You have to stay alert.
有男朋友陪吗?
Is your boyfriend with you?
我哪有男朋友
I don't have one.
Farceda  美薇也在  你们说两句
Fareeda, }meiwei is here, have a chat with her.
-Fareeda  新年快乐  -爸爸
- Fareeda, happy new year! - Dad.
-你那卡了  爸爸  -我是美薇
- Dad, I'm losing you... - Meiwei here... Fareeda... Hello?
Juma  走  开车
Juma, let's go!
是信号不好
Yes, as always,
每次你让她跟我说话都信号不好
whenever I want to start a conversation.
我觉得她还没接受我
She's avoiding me.
不会的
No way!
你想太多了
Don't over-react.
出来
Get out!
快点儿  快
Come on, now!
快走
Move!
老板
Sir,
要客秦国立被劫持
the qin couple has been kidnapped.
有报警吗?
Did you call the police?
已经报警
Just called them.
今天是唐人街春节大巡游
There's a Chinese new year parade.
该区有几十万游客
There are thousands of revellers,
所有道路已被封锁
all roads are blocked.
警力到达需要一段时间
The police will take time to respond.
有没有秦国立的定位?
Where is qin?
正在移动
On the move
还在唐人街区域
but still in Chinatown.
我们有没有队员在附近?
Are therevanguards in the area?
有两名休假的队员就在附近
Two off-dutyvanguards nearby.
立即派他们去营救秦国立
Send them to rescue qin guoli right away.
收到
Yes, sir!
一
One.
二
Two.
三
Three.
真厉害
Amazing!
看干爹给你买的这是什么?
See what godfather has brought you?
干爹  这个是什么?
Godfather, who is that?
这是中国英雄
Captain China!
像不像你爸爸
He looks just like your dad.
爸爸就是中国英雄
Captain China is my dad!
我们的VIP客户被绑架
Our vip clients are kidnapped.
需要紧急支援
Emergency deployment requested.
距离你们位置四百米
About 400m from your current location.
两位小心
Stay alert!
明白
Copy that!
妈  我们得走了
Mom, we need to go.
嘉华  乖乖跟小姨在一块儿玩
Jiahua, keep your aunt amused. There!
坐下
Sit down!
下午好啊  秦先生
Good afternoon, mr qin.
你们是什么人?
Who are you people?
是你把Omar父亲的行踪透露给美国人吧
You betrayed Omar's father's location to the Americans, didn't you?
没有  我不知道他父亲的行踪
No, I didn't know where his father was.
Omar他
Omar's...
还活着?
Still alive?
那些财产
The money!
Omar父亲的财产
Omar's father's money,
在你那里吗?
do you have it?
没有
No,
我不知道
I don't know.
他是你丈夫?
Is he your husband?
是
Yes...
求你不要伤害我妻子
Please, don't hurt my wife.
-老公  -求你
Honey - no, please
听我解释
let me explain.
这事儿跟她没关系
She has nothing to do with this!
老公
Honey...
你知道失去亲人的滋味吗?
Do you know what it's like to lose your loved ones?
秦先生
Mr qin!
钱呢
The money!
快说
Tell me!
我们到位了
We're in position.
带枪了吗?
Brought your gun?
休假带什么枪啊?
No, it's my day off.
你带了?
What about you?
带了
Of course!
在他们那儿呢
It's with them.
掩护我
Cover me.
先生  我们关门了
Sir, we are closed.
关门了?
Closed?
是的
Yes.
我是这里的老板
I'm the boss!
管你是谁
I don't care.
没枪
He's unarmed.
分头行动
Let's split up.
杀了她
Kill her!
不要
No, no!
求你
Please...
我知道那笔财产在哪儿
I know where the money is.
很好
Good.
只要你把全部财产交出来
Hand over the money to me
我不会伤害你
and I won't hurt you
还有你的老婆
or your wife.
你好
Hi.
今天不营业
We're closed today.
你的狼崽需要你
Your puppy needs you.
快走
Run!
跟我来
Come with me!
抓住她
Get her!
快走
Run!
进去
Go inside.
快走
C'mon. Go.
躲起来
Take cover.
凯旋你在哪儿?
Kaixuan, where are you?
我炸猪蹄呢
I'm frying a pig's knuckle!
只是一个安保
He's just security.
把秦国立交给我就放你走
Hand over qin guoli to me and I will let you leave.
只是份工作而已
It's just a job,
何必这么拼命?
why risk your life over it?
你也是打工的
They don't pay enough for you
干嘛这么拼命?
to work this hard.
你是谁啊?
Who are you?
跳
Jump!
我是"急先锋"的
I'm fromvanguard!
别开枪
Don't shoot.
我要活的
We need him alive.
弥雅  你在哪儿?
Miya, where are you?
还有三十秒  马上就到
I'm 30 seconds away.
快
Hurry... C'mon.
快上车
Get in, quick!
别开枪
Don't shoot!
他受伤了
He's hurt.
没事儿吧
You alright?
没事儿
I'm okay.
劫持秦先生的这伙人
The gang that captured qin
是来自"北极狼"的
are from the arctic wolves.
带头的人叫Broto
Their leader is broto.
只要有钱什么都干
They'll do anything for money.
"北极狼"怎么会盯上你呢?
Why are they after you?
以前我在中东有个合作伙伴叫Maasym
I had a business partner called maasym.
我替他在欧洲卖石油
I made him a fortune
可是后来我发现
I only found out later
他竟然是"复仇者组织"的头领
he ran the gang brotherhood of vengeance.
那时我想脱离他已经来不及了
I tried to quit but it was too late.
Maasym他威胁我
Maasym forced me
让我帮他安排资金
to arrange funds for him
来购买大规模杀伤性武器
to buy weapons of mass destruction,
如果我不从
or he would kill me
他会杀了我  还有我的家人
and my family.
后来
Later,
我向伦敦警方举报他
I tipped off the London police
提供了Maasym的资料
about him.
七个月前
美军把Maasym给炸死了
Maasym was killed in a military operation.
他的长子Omar却活了下来
His eldest son Omar survived.
"北极狼"是Omar派来的
So Omar sent the arctic wolves?
是的
Yes.
他们如果在这里抓不到我
If they can't get me,
一定会去抓我女儿
they'll go after my daughter.
请你立刻派人去把我女儿带回来
Can you send someone
可以吗?
to bring her back?
她现在在哪儿?
Where's she now?
她在非洲
Africa.
这个我会安排
I'll see to it.
谢谢
Thank you.
老板  Broto
Boss, broto.
人被救走了
He's saft.
被谁救走了?
Taken away by who?
他们  自称"急先锋"
They call themselves vanguard.
"急先锋"是什么?
What'svanguard?
"急先锋"是一家民营国际安保公司
Vanguard is an international private security company
成员主要来自国际退役军警
most of them are retired military
和安保专家
or security experts.
他们的服务包括安保运输和要员保护
Their services include security for shipping, and vip protection.
够了
Enough!
秦国立还有一个女儿
Qin has a daughter.
把她给我带来
Bring her to me
不管他躲在哪个洞穴
and he will scurry out of whatever hole
都会乖乖爬出来
he's crawled into, okay?
收到
Yes, sir!
老板
Sir,
伦敦警方已经核实
the intel from qin
秦国立所说内容属实
has been verified by the London police.
好的
Good.
这个女孩一个人跑来非洲保护野生动物
The girl went alone to protect African wildlife
还冒险拍到这些非法盗猎的画面
and risked her life recording poachers.
很勇敢
She's brave.
她在非洲野生动物保护志愿者中
Among wildlife conservationists,
还是比较活跃的
she's an activist.
在非洲
In Africa,
每年有三万头大象
30,000 elephants
被盗猎者非法猎杀
are slaughtered by hunters every year.
我现在还挺佩服她的
I have great respect for her.
你看她的视频
Just look at her video,
上传不到一个小时
uploaded an hour ago,
就有四十多万的点击量
Has 400,000 pic...
现在我们又多了一帮敌人
now we have more adversaries.
赶快找到她
We must find her quickly.
我们有理由相信
We have reason to believe that
被杀的志愿者和这些盗猎者有关
the volunteers were victims of a group of poachers
盗猎者的头领叫吞达
led by a man named tunda.
像他这样的杀人犯应该被关起来
Murderous scum like him should be locked up!
我要她死
I want her dead!
吞达
Tunda!
最近怎么样?  朋友
How's it going, my friend?
很开心见到你
Good to see you.
看看你  超级明星
Look at you, superstar!
一小时就四十万的点击量
400,000 clicks in one hour.
不错啊  兄弟
Not bad, my brother.
闭嘴吧
Shut up!
那个女孩
This girl,
我一定要找到她
I'm gonna find her
然后宰了她
and kill her.
我们也在找她  来
We're looking for her, too.
我介绍你认识一下我的老板
Come on, let me introduce you to my boss.
老板  这是吞达
Hey, boss, this is tunda,
非洲最好的猎人
the best hunter in all of Africa.
你能找到那个女孩吗?
Can you find the girl?
这个多管闲事的贱货
Bicth...
她说有119人被杀了
She said the kill count was 1197?
一旦抓住她
Once I get to her,
我会让她成为第120个
I'm going to make it an even 120!
你猎动物  我猎人
You hunt animals, I hunt people.
我们的区别就是
The only difference is,
我要活捉我的猎物
I got my trophy taken alive.
这些是给你的订金
Here's your deposit for now.
完事后还有更丰厚的
You'll get the big bucks once you complete the hunt.
我们去打猎吧
Let's go hunting!
出发  去打猎
Yeah! Go hunting! Let's go!
爽啊  去打猎
Yeah! Yeah! Go hunting!
Charlie  过来  Charlie  来
Charlie, come. Charlie, come on!
好重
Weght...
她在那边
There she is.
Juma  他们是什么人?
Juma, who are they?
我不知道啊
I don't know.
你是Fareeda吗?
Are you fareeda?
我是
Yes.
这里有狮子  你不能过来
There are lions here. Back off.
Charlie  别动
Charlie, stay.
我去
Gosh,
真有狮子
they're real lions!
站着比它凶就行了
Stand your ground!
我们受你父亲秦国立所托
Your father sent us
来这里接你
to come and fetch you.
这些人就是来绑架你的
They're here to kidnap you!
赶快过来
Come over now!
震宇  快去接她
Lei, go get her!
Charlic  退后
Charlie, back.
老板
Sir,
有狮子
lions on the loose!
一个女孩子不怕  你怕什么?
What are you afraid of?
狮子是公的
It's a male.
不是也有母的吗?
There's also a lioness.
别动
Stay!
她在那儿
She's over there.
拿枪
Get the guns!
Yes, sir
Yes, sir.
跟我走
Follow me.
在那儿
There!
除了Fareeda全部给我杀光
Kill them all except fareeda.
该死
Damn you!
又是"急先锋"
Vanguard again!
跟着我
Stay with me.
去抓那个女孩  快
Get the girl, now!
这个女孩会得到她应得的
This girl, she's gonna get what she deserves.
你干什么?  我们要活的
What are you doing? We need her alive.
什么都行
Whatever...
上车
Get in!
出来过来
Get out! Come on!
Charlie!
救我
Help me!
Charlic  救我
Charlie! Help me!
Charlic  过来
Charlie, over here!
什么Charlie啊?
Who's Charlie?
快叫他来帮忙
Tell him to hurry.
带她先跑
Leave with her now. Get in. C'm on!
吞达快来帮我
Tunda, come help!
快啊
Hurry!
快帮我
Help me!
Charlie!
Charlie  别过去
Charlie, go away!
Charlie!
松手吧
Let go!
它不听我的了
He's ignoring me.
你们千万别动
Don't move!
别动
Hold still!
你们怎么都不听我的了
Why is no one listening?
千万别跑
Don't run!
快躺  下装死
Lie down and play dead!
我死
I am dead
什么?
what?
快点  我们走
Come on, let's go.
快  点
Go, go, go!
快
Quick!
快追别让我的猎物跑了
Keep going! Don't let my trophy get away!
不要
No, no.
竟然让她跑了
You let her get away!
还自称是非洲最好的猎人
The best hunter in Africa? My ass!
连一个女人都抓不到
You can't even hunt down a woman.
我是最好的  是因为我有耐心
I'm the best because I have Patience.
即使狗也懂耐心的价值
Even hyenas understand the cost of Patience.
为了抓到猎物
They wait hours, even days,
它们愿意花几个小时  甚至几天去等待
before they get their prey.
我付钱不是为了听你讲鬛狗的故事
I didn't pay for you to preach about hyenas.
她只是走运而已
She just got lucky.
抓到她
Bring her to me,
否则你就是我的猎物
or you'll become my prey.
现在
Now,
前面是什么地方?
what's up ahead?
丛林而已
It's just a jungle.
跟着我
Follow me.
你的枪打什么的?
What do you use the gun for?
打大象的
Elephants.
Juma你没事吧?
Juma, are you okay?
你怎么样?
What about you?
我还挺得住
I'll manage...
袁旭
Yuanxu,
什么情况?
what's the status?
我们监测到雷震宇
We've located lei
距离你二十公里的原始森林区域
20km away in the jungle,
正在往西南方向移动
moving towards the southwest.
该区域地形复夺
Vehicles can't pass through a primeval forest.
你们只能徒步
Go on foot,
要注意安全
and be careful!
弥雅  快送他们到医院
Miya, take them to the hospital.
好  小心
Ok - be careful
老板
sir!
不是叫你送他们吗?
You should be taking them to hospital.
你来  干嘛?
What are you doing here?
Jonathan还能开车
Jonathan can drive.
我跟你一起去
I'll go with you.
走
Come on, then.
呼叫伦敦总部
Calling London hq,
请回答
please come in.
收到
Roger that.
已经锁定雷震宇的位置
We've located lei.
我们根据雷的定位推断
The coordinates show
他和Farccda应该在鸟类观测站
he and fareeda are in an avian observatory.
当前生命体征基本正常
His vital signs are normal.
收到
Copy that.
快点
Keep moving.
到了已经天亮了
We need to get there before daybreak.
醒了
Awake?
这什么鸟啊?
What kind of bird is that?
你看看
Take a look. Okay.
这个叫天堂鸟
Bird of paradise!
这种鸟啊
These birds
一生追求自由和幸福
spend their lives searching for happiness and freedom.
它们遇到喜欢的同类
When they meet their own kind,
还会跳舞
they dance for each other.
这儿的原住民用它们的羽毛
Tribal people used their feathers
做成装饰品
to decorate themselves.
十九世纪开始风靡欧洲
They're prized in Europe in the 19th century.
因为
But because of
过度捕杀
excessive hunting,
它们现在已变成稀有鸟类了
they're so rare now.
非洲狮为伴
You hang out with lions,
天堂鸟为邻
and exotic birds.
爱好自由
You're a carefree spirit,
享受浪漫
a romantic at heart,
追求梦想
in pursuit of your dreams.
你是处女座吧
You must be a Virgo.
你才是处女座呢
I think you're a Virgo.
你怎么知道的
How could you tell?
你真是处女座啊?
Are you really?
快点
Faster, faster!
就在前面大树那里
Right behind the big tree!
我们走
Let's go! Let's go!
马上离开这里
Let's get out of here. Sure.
直走  就在前面一百米
Go straight. They're 100m ahead.
这次不能让他们再跑了
Don't let them get away!
有二辆不明身份的吉普车
Two unidentified vehicles
朝雷震宇驶去
are heading for lei.
预计三分钟内抵达
They're three minutes away.
好的
Ok.
收到
Got it.
快去  攻击
Go, attack!
老板解决了
Got 'em all, sir.
快走
Let's go. Once more.
老板  上车
Hop in, sir!
小心  躲开
Move over,
我来
let me...
他们来了
They're coming! - Hurry! - Move!
快追
Hurry up, hurry!
抓紧
Hold on tight!
上次让她侥幸跑了
She did get lucky last time.
这次绝对不行
This won't happen again.
记住别开枪  我要活捉她
No bullets, I want her taken alive.
上
Go, go, go!
再快点
Faster!
靠近点
Closer! Go!
处女座  救我
Virgo, help me!
插死你
Chopstick!
再近点
Fareeda - get closer!
快走
Go! Go!
Fareeda!
处女座
Virgo...
救我
Help!
撑住啊  弥雅
Hang in there, Miya!
上
Go!
滚开
Get away!
滚开放开我
Get away! Get off me!
不要
No!
救我
Help me, sir!
Help!
弥雅
Miya!
我们躲不开了
We're done for.
准备
Brace yourself, jump!
这里
Here!
在这里
叫什么叫
Over here!
叫他们也听不见
What are you yelling for?
这里啊
They can't hear you!
Over here! We're here!
秦国立拿走了
Qin guoli has assets
我们"复仇者组织"的财产
belonging to the brotherhood of vengeance.
你们说"急先锋"不会放弃任何人
You say vanguard leaves no man behind.
那给我听好了
So listen to me carefully.
把秦国立交给我们
Deliver qin guoli to us
就放你的人走
and I'll let your man go.
如果不答应条件
If you fail to make this exchange,
他就会被处决
they'll be beheaded.
我愿意去交换人质
I volunteer myself
只要能把我女儿换回来
for the release of my daughter
还有你的队员一起
and your colleague.
你不要去
No, you mustn't.
太危险了
It's dangerous.
一定还有其他办法的
There must be another way.
没事的
I'll be fine,
你放心
trust me.
我能单独跟你聊聊吗?
May I have a word in private?
可以
Of course.
你出去一下
Give us a minute.
没事的
I'll be fine.
你还有什么瞒我?
What are you hiding?
Massym在海外的资产
I'm the only one who knows
只有我一个人知道藏在哪里
where maasym's assets are.
我必须和Omar做个了断
I must settle the score with Omar.
唐先生
Mr tang,
如果这些资产
if they use this money
被他们拿来买武器
to buy more weapons,
就会有很多无辜的人牺牲
many lives will be at stake.
关乎无辜人的生命
Protecting the innocents
我们"急先锋"责无旁贷
is our Paramount duty.
谢谢
Thank you.
归根结底
Greed...
都是贪心带来的祸
Is the root of all evils.
二  三  四
One, two, three, four...
-嘉华  你来啦  -五  六  七
- Hi, jiahua. - Five, six, seven,
八  九
eight, nine.
爸爸  礼物
Dad, this is for you.
儿子
My dear boy!
你们怎么来了?
What brings you here?
他非要过来给你送礼物
He wants to give you a present.
礼物?  为什么要给爸爸礼物啊?
Present? What for?
我就是想给你礼物
Because I wanted to.
因为今天是你的生日啊
It's your birthday today!
爸爸连自己生日都忘了
Daddy is so absent-minded!
我们还在等待支援
We're still waiting for the support...
我们一会儿再开
Hold on just one sec...
好
OK
这是谁啊?
Who's that?
这是爸爸
That's daddy.
-爸爸?  你就是他心目中的中国队长
- Daddy? - To him, you are captain China.
是吗?  我们刚在家怎么说的
- Really? - What did we discuss?
中国队长怎么样?
What about captain China?
中国队长比美国队长
He's mightier than captain America!
厉害  厉害
He's awesome!
来  击掌
Give me five!
那爸爸也没这么高大威猛啊
But he's much stronger than me.
爸爸最高大
Daddy's the strongest!
来  乖乖亲一个
Now give daddy a kiss.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you,
happy birthday to you!
祝凯旋生日快乐
Happy birthday to kaixuan,
祝你生日快乐
happy birthday to you.
谢谢老板谢谢大家
Thank you, sir. Thanks everyone.
我许个愿吧
I'll make a wish,
我希望震宇能安全回来
for lei's safe return.
爸爸好棒好棒
Daddy's awesome!
来你给大家分一下吧
Please share the cake.
好的
Okay.
给你个小熊猫
Here, a baby panda for you!
拿着吧
Take it.
说谢谢叔叔
Take it. And say: Thank you, sir.
谢谢叔叔
Thank you, sir.
什么叔叔  叫哥哥
Just call me bro!
哥哥
Bro!
对了
Right.
叫她阿姨
Call her auntie.
叫阿姨
嘉华  叫姐姐
Sis would do.
好了  我们跟姐姐出去吧
Good boy. Okay, let's go out with sis,
-不要打扰爸爸了  -去吧
and let daddy get back to work
跟阿姨玩去吧
go play with auntie.
不许教坏小孩子
Stop misleading children!
这小子加入我们"急先锋"
Lei has been withvanguard
应该五年了吧
for five years?
五年三个月零二十八天
Five years, three months and 28 days, sir.
这次行动相对比较复杂
This operation is challenging.
而且你的伤还没好
Since you're still recuperating,
你留下来做后勤支援吧
why don't you stay behind as back-up?
老板你到底想说什么?
Sir, don't worry, I'm fine.
儿子画的?
Your boy drew this?
是
Yes.
说实话
Quite frankly,
这次我也没有绝对把握
I'm not sure how this would turn out.
嘉华已经没有妈妈了
Jiahua has already lost his mom.
你应该留下来照顾他
You should stay
我想成为儿子的骄傲
to look after him.
您现在在做行政工作
You are now our ceo,
就别去了
you don't have to go.
我有责任把所有队员带回来
I've a duty to bring my team back. Fine,
我们一起去
then let's go together.
语儿
Linda,
我们考虑一下做些徽章
I think we should
挂在胸前蛮漂亮的
order some of these.
好看
Gorgeous.
Gorgeous!
那是
Really?
给你
For you.
谢谢
Thank you.
贾德巴拉全城共有五万人口
Jiadebala population is 50,000 citizens.
有两千多人组成了Omar的武装力量
2,000 of them are Omar's fighters.
他们利用此地区作为训练基地
They use the area as a training ground.
由于该地区地形复杂
Due to the rugged terrain,
政府目前无力收复
the government couldn't take it back.
现在我们最需要的是情报支持
We need more intel before we go in.
我们有没有内线?
Do we have anyone on the ground?
有的  有个线人
Yes, we have a source.
正在联络
He's on it.
好的
Good.
这里是我们从未涉足过的地区
We are entering uncharted territories,
困难是前所未有的
we'll be up against extreme dangers.
我知道大家都是和平精英
You are the best of the best,
厚德守信
virtuous and trustworthy,
忠诚尽责
loyal and reliable.
为了我们的责任
For our obligations,
为了我们的战友
for our comrades-in-arms,
必须战胜一切不可能
we must overcome all odds!
我们一定要
We have to return
凯旋归来
triumphantly!
In triumph!
凯旋归来
我们一起凯旋归来
We will return victorious!
凯旋归来
Victorious!
出发
Let's go!
行动
Move!
贾德巴拉古城有上千年的历史文化古迹
Jiadebala dates back a thousand years.
有大量的文物
It's home to many priceless relics.
"复仇者组织"占领后
When the brotherhood captured the city,
就是依靠贩卖文物和走私毒品
they sold off artefacts, smuggled drugs
获得巨额的财富
and made a fortune.
城内的无辜百姓都成为他们的人质
The locals have become their hostages.
如果政府军强攻的话
If government forces were to attack,
我想整座千年古城恐泊会毁于一旦
the city can be destroyed overnight.
喀拉苏带我们见的这位朋友靠谱吗?
Can we trust kalasu's friend?
他会帮我们吗?
Will he help us?
阿巴提是当地最好的厨师
Abati is the best chef around.
被毒贩枪杀了
Killed...
被挟持的人质  Fareeda
This is the hostage fareeda.
还有我们的队员雷
Lei is one of ours.
我们要找到他们
We cannot leave them behind.
你知道的
You know what it's like
想救你在乎的人是什么感觉
to wanna save someone you care about.
我能帮助你和家人离开这里
I can help you and your family
开始新的生活
start a new life somewhere else.
我只需要你带我们进入城堡
I just need your help to get us inside the fortress.
我只能送她进去
I can only transport her.
其他人可以从无人防守区进去
Rest of the team have to take the unguarded route.
为什么没有把守?
Why are there no guards?
很险要
It's rough.
你们打算怎么逃出来?
How are you gonna escape?
我们有个计划
We've a plan,
但需要您的帮助
but we need your help.
开门  穆罕默德
Open up, Mohammed.
是我  阿巴提
This is abati.
这里我能带你们来的最接近城堡的地方
This is the closest I can get you to the fortress.
我现在得走了
I have to go now.
穆罕默德是我的人
Mohammed is my man.
会留下保护你们
He'll take care of you. Okay. Come.
我化这个妆
This special war paint
是为了暴露的时候
will save me from getting killed
不被你们误伤
by friendly fire.
这两台防弹车是Omar专用的
These two bulletproof vehicles
按装甲车的规格
are specially modified for Omar,
特别改装过
just like armoured cars.
他们真的会把我们杀掉吗?
Will they really kill us?
我不想这么早死掉
I don't want to die so young.
让我看看你的右手
Show me your right palm.
放心吧
Don't worry,
你不会死的
you'll survive.
为什么?
Why?
因为你的生命线很长啊
You have a long life line. What's this?
放心吧"急先锋"会来救我们的
Don't worry, vanguard will come for us.
什么呀?
But how?
告诉你一个好的消息
I have good news for you.
你的父亲很快会来
Your father is on his way,
你老板也会来
and your boss, too.
带他出去
Get him out.
你们想干嘛?
What do you want?
你们要带他去哪儿?
Where are you taking him?
你们要带他去哪儿啊?
你和我们"北极狼"挺有缘啊
We're destined to cross paths again.
第一次你从我们手上把人带走
First you snatched someone from our grasp.
这次我们把你拿下
This time I have you captured.
能跟我们打平手的人不多
Not many can get even with us.
我老板很欣赏你
My boss sees something special in you.
如果你跟着我们干
Work with us,
一年挣的钱够你花一辈子
you'll earn more in a year
你知道吗?
than a lifetime.
我和你们不一样
We are different.
不都是拿命赚钱?
We both risk lives for money.
有什么不一样?
What's so different?
知足  知不足
Be content, know your weaknesses.
有为
Things you do,
有不为
things you don't.
你什么意思?
What are you talking about?
我听不懂
I don't understand.
不要放纵自己的欲望
Never indulge in desire.
要有自知之明
Know yourself.
应该做的事  必须要做
Know what you should do,
不该做的事  必不能做
know what you shouldn't do.
你学会了我们的语言
You've learned our tongue,
没能学会我们的文化
but not our ethics.
老板他说…
Boss, he says that...
错误的选择
Big mistake.
带他出去
Take him away.
雷震宇身上被绑上了炸弹衣
They're strapping a bomb vest on lei,
带有定时引爆器
with a timer.
"急先锋"答应带秦国立来交换人质
Vanguard has promised to bring qin in exchange for the hostages.
但我不相信他们
But I wouldn't trust them.
他们肯定会设法营救
They will attempt a rescue.
我们的城堡建立了几千年
In the millennia since our fortress was built,
坚不可摧
there's never been a breach.
我们的战士从小接受训练
Our warriors have been trained since boyhood.
我们还是应该采取防备措施
We should still take precaution.
加强戒备
Step up security
随时准备开枪
and shoot on sight.
老板
Boss.
什么计划?
What's the plan?
交易仍然有效
The deal is still on.
钱准备好了吗?
Did you prepare the money?
是的
Yes.
交易的时间和地点
Time and location of exchange?
我会再告诉你
I will let you know.
-大家晚上好  -晚上好啊
- Good evening, brothers. - Good evening.
-试试我的点心  拿去  -真客气
- Come try some snacks. - Thank you.
先走啦
Got to go.
走吧
Go!
我靠
Holy shit!
戴着防毒面具怎么还那么臭
Even wearing my mask, this place reeks like hell!
我快受不了啦
I can't stand it anymore.
赶紧爬啊
Keep moving!
防毒面具它不防臭啊
The masks are no match for the smells.
太臭了
Too stinky.
十二点钟方向
At twelve o'clock,
发现四名武装人
four gunmen
他们正在向北移动
are heading north.
三点钟方位
At three o'clock,
有一位武装人员正在原地戒备
one armed man is standing guard.
南部方位没有发现任何情况
All clear on the south side.
你们去那边巡逻
You do your usual beat.
我们进来了
We're in.
敌方守卫没有异常情况
Everything's normal.
你们可以按计划分头行动
Split up as planned.
收到
Copy that.
Laila今晚她留在你这儿
Laila, she stays with you tonight.
好的
Okay.
明天我带你进入Omar的城堡
I'll bring you to Omar's compound tomorrow.
麻烦把灯关了
Please turn off the light.
好的
Yes.
炸弹好了
Explosive all set go!
已发现雷震宇在天台位置
We've located lei on the rooftop.
雷震宇的十二点方向
There are two snipers
有两名狙击手埋伏
lurking at twelve o'clock.
他们来了
They are here.
让我们来打中国鸭子
Let's shoot some Chinese ducks.
我已经就位了
I'm in position.
你最好先离开
You'd better leave now. Okay.
爸
Dad, dad...
别动
Don't move! Dad...
我是"急先锋"的头儿
I'm the head of vanguard.
负责这次交换人质
Let's make the exchange.
我看你说话像个头儿
You speak with the conviction and impatience of a man in charge,
但在这儿我说了算
but you're not in charge here!
秦先生  你带了我要的东西吗?
Mr qin, have you brought me what I asked for?
拿来
Come on, give it to me.
他们已经进入陷阱
Target is in the trap,
我们会干掉他们
we'll finish them.
这是什么?
What is this bullshit?
这是我帮你父亲管理的财产清单
That's the list of your father's assets I managed.
他把大部分资产都兑换成了黄金
He converted most of them into gold
但是藏在了一个安全的地方
but hid it away in a secure place.
我可以带你去
I can take you there.
兑现承诺吧
Honour your promise,
放了Fareeda和雷
release fareeda and lei.
除非我先拿到我的财产
Not until I have the assets.
我听说"急先锋"从不放弃任何队员
I heardvanguard never leaves anyone behind.
我今天就想验证一下
I'd like to test that theory.
是我的话就赶紧说再见
I would say my goodbyes quickly.
秦先生
Mr qin,
你女儿的死期到了
your daughter's time is up!
不  求你  把她的头砍下来
No, stop! - No, please. - Cut her head down!
什么情况
What's going on?
不要动
Stop!
看你的胸口
Look at your chest.
放下武器
Drop the gun,
告诉他们放下枪
tell everybody drop their guns!
所有人不许碰她
Nobody gets hurt.
所有人都把枪放下
Everybody drop your guns.
我踩着跳雷
I'm standing on bouncing mines!
封锁所有城堡出口
Block all the gates!
趴下
Hit the deck!
凯旋来不及了
Kaixuan, we've no time!
先解决你身上这个
Let's deal with the vest first.
别管我  你们走
Don't worry about me, just go!
少废话
Cut the bullshit!
他们太鬼了
They're so sneaky.
剪哪条线都会炸
Whichever wire I cut will set it off.
快走吧
Just leave.
把电池冷冻就爆不了
I can deactivate the bomb by freezing the battery.
还有跳雷
Now the bouncing mines!
凯旋解决不了的
Kaixuan, there's nothing you can do.
你还有儿子  你不能死
You have a son. You need to stay alive.
快走  快走吧
Just go! Run!
脚离开后
Take your feet off,
跳雷弹起1.2米就会爆炸
the mines will bounce up and explode mid-air,
杀伤半径14米
decimating everything within 14 metres.
建平  背后
Jianping, behind you!
延龙
Yanlong!
你先撤
You go first. Okay.
我数一二三
On my count of three,
一起跳
jump!
一
One,
二
two,
三
three,
跳
jump!
走
Let's go.
在那里
Over there!
干掉他
Shoot him down!
救Farceda
Go help fareeda! Go!
跟紧我
Stay with me. Go!
我不能中枪
I can't be shot.
我也不能中枪啊
Me neither!
他们在这儿都过来
They're over here! Here.
别动
Don't move.
接着
Catch it.
撤
Pull out!
来人啊
Come...
快点  快点
We need everyone!
所有人都快去
On the double!
Omar需要支援
Omar needs help!
穆罕默德  跟我来
Mohammed, come with me.
封锁所有出口
Block all the exits!
所有人到自己位置
Hold your positions
封锁大门
and lock the gate!
没事吧?
Are you alright?
没事儿
I'm fine.
走
Let's go.
后方街道有阿巴提和穆罕默德
Abati and Mohammed are just blocks away
驾驶车辆前来接应
on their way to pick you up.
这里
This way, quick!
延龙补位
Yanlong, cover me. Copy!
上
Go! Move!
给你
Take this.
救人
Move him!
挺住
Hang in there! Let's go!
周斌撤
Zhou, pull out! Go.
快上车
Get in, quick!
上车  快
Get in.
撤  我掩护
Pull out, I'll cover! Copy!
上车  快
Get in, quick!
走  快走
Go, go, go... Go!
火箭筒
Rpg!
凯旋
Kaixuan!
已经探测不到张凯旋的生命体征
I can't detect kaixuan's vital signs.
凯旋已经失去生命迹象啦
His vital signs are gone!
都给我上
Go, come on.
我们被包围了
They're closing in.
再不走我们都走不了了
We need to go now or be trapped.
让我去把他救回来
I'll find kaixuan and bring him back.
去  小心
Sure, be safe!
掩护
Cover him!
Yes, sir!
延龙
Yanlong,
怎么样?
are you alright?
-没事儿  -走
- I'm okay. - Let's go.
凯旋
Kaixuan!
快点
Hurry up.
兄弟  顶住啊
Hang in there, bro!
撤
Pull out!
快撤  再不走就来不及了
Go now or it'll be too late!
走啊快走
Go, let's go!
他们要的是我
They just want me!
秦国立
Qin!
-你回来  -停
- You come back! - Stop, stop!
快走
Come back!
把我女儿带走  快点
Take my daughter out of here! Quick!
记得我们的约定
Remember our deal.
爸  不要…
Dad, don't...
爸
Dad. Dad!
-快  -进来
Get in. Quick - come on
都别开枪
Nobody shoots!
挺住
Hang in there!
兄弟  你不能死
Buddy, don't die on me.
不能死
Stay alive!
凯旋  你给我起来
Kaixuan, wake up!
你的儿子嘉华
Remember your son jiahua.
你说过你要成为他的英雄
You said you'd be his hero.
这都是你说的
You promised!
你给我起来
Wake up now!
起来
up now!
起来呀
C'm on!
凯旋  你给我起来
Kaixuan, wake up.
起来啊
Wake up, you hear me?
小心  趴下
Hold tight! Take cover!
抓稳了
Hold tight!
兄弟
Stop, dear...
别按了  疼
Don't...
这一路颠  颠对了
Thanks to my rollercoaster ride!
你刚才是不是亲我了?
Did you just kiss me?
你得对我负责任啊
I'm all yours now!
我儿子送我的
My son gave me this.
还是咱们儿子最好
Our son is the best!
放心  你爸爸不会有事
Relax, your father will be fine.
他们需要他
They need him alive.
我知道去哪儿找他们
I know where to find them.
跟踪器
Tracking device.
我不喜欢严刑逼供
I don't like torture
我更不喜欢废话
as much as I don't like bullshit.
是你出卖了我父亲吗?
Did you betray my father?
没有
No.
黄金在哪儿?
Where is the gold?
迪拜
Dubai.
我带你去
I'll take you there.
别伤害我
Don't hurt me.
Omar父亲刚付了购买大规模
Omar's father paid a deposit
杀伤性武器的订金
on weapons of mass destruction.
交易还没完成  他就死了
But he was killed before the deal went through.
他们在迪拜的某处藏匿了两个亿
They have more than $200m stowed somewhere in Dubai
我们必须要在他们交易时一网打尽
we'll have to catch them in the act of making the deal.
根据你们提供的"北极狼"情报
Based on your intel information of the arctic wolves,
我们已查到了全部该组织成员的资料
we found information on every arctic wolves mercenary.
其中两名成员已于今早入境
Two of them entered Dubai this morning,
目前已在我们的监控之下
and they are under our surveillance.
我们现在还不确定他们是否与绑架秦国立
We cannot confirm if they are connected with the kidnapping of qin
以及这次武器交易有关
or the arms deal.
老板
Sir,
这次行动我们可以带枪吗?
can we carry firearms?
不行
No,
你们只能协助和协商调查
you will be only assisting and consulting with the investigation.
所有的行动
All field operations here
都由我们迪拜警方负责
are going to be carried out by our police force.
你会听中文?
You understand Chinese?
我能听懂
I can understand,
但不太会说
though I don't speak much.
我的老婆是中国人
My wife is Chinese.
中国人
Chinese!
肯定很漂亮
Must be beautiful.
当然
Absolutely.
这个就是Mardct
This is marder.
他是个好色之徒
He's a serial womaniser.
前女友都是小演员和模特儿
Loves dating models and small-time actresses.
而且有暴力倾向
He has a violent temper.
一年前
Arrested last year
他因为殴打女友被拘留
for beating up a girlfriend.
大写的渣男
A typical scumbag!
今天下午游泳池见
I'll see you at the pool this afternoon.
我们最好能拷贝到他们的手机
Best if we can hack his phones
和信用卡信息
and credit cards.
摸清他们的底细
Then we can find out more.
这没问题
No problem.
但是这两个人反侦察能力非常强
But they are careful and alert,
很难靠近
hard to infiltrate.
那咱们就用美人计
How about a honeytrap?
好主意
Brilliant!
你们看着我干嘛?
Why are you staring at me?
你们平时不是说我像个爷们吗?
Didn't you always say I'm one of the boys?
还美人计
Forget honeytrap,
做不了
not me!
凯旋哥
Kaixuan,
要不你来?
how about you?
还真是小心啊
Not taking any chances huh?
来换个姿势
Change the pose.
很好  继续
Great, a little more.
来  拨弄拨弄头发
Good. Stroke your hair.
特别棒特别美
Good. Nice posture.
来  多一点  对
A little more, great!
在泳池里谈生意真好
Not a bad conference room for the day.
完全同意
I'm with you on that.
很好
Wonderful!
来  转个身
Turn around...
对  大笑
Great!
特别美
Sweet!
位置不错保持啊  别动
Great pose! Hold it right there...
很好  光线很美啊
Very good, the lighting is beautiful.
我们再来几张
Let's take a few more photos
货两天内必须送到迪拜
the merchandise must be delivered to Dubai in two days.
你们能保证安全进港吗?
Can you guarantee its safe passage into the port?
当然
Yes!
我们的货不需要进港
Our goods doesn't even have to enter the port.
它可以远程遥控
It can be controlled remotely.
但这交易被你们拖了一年
But you've delayed it for one year.
所以要完成交易还要两个亿
So if you want to finish the deal, it's still $200m.
只要现金
Only cash.
钱到货到
You'll get what you pay for.
稍等我一下
I'll get back to you shortly.
没问题
Sure.
好  差不多了
We are almost done here.
我们去沙滩那边拍吧
Let's shoot some more at the beach.
亲爱的  我们换身衣服再拍啊
Darling, let's get changed first.
怎么样?
How's it going?
他是中东
He works for Josef,
头号军火贩子尤瑟夫的人
a major arms dealer in the middle east.
想办法拷贝他们的手机卡
Let's find ways to hack their phones.
什么事?
What's happening?
那三个亚洲人很可疑
I believe the three asians
一直往你那边拍照
have been taking pictures of you.
亲爱的
Darling,
没阳光了  咱们得抓点紧了
we need to hurry to catch the light.
好的
Sure.
你好
Hi, good day!
快去沙滩  没光了
To the beach now. Light's fading.
你们想的什么破美人计
So much for your honeytrap!
我都穿成那样了
Dressing up like this
他都不理我
and he still ignores me.
我就问你她漂不漂亮?
Don't you think she's beautiful?
漂亮
Of course.
漂亮到我都不好意思看了
So gorgeous I can't even bear to look!
他们在沙滩上拍照
They are still taking pictures on the beach.
所以?
So?
我觉得他们没什么
I think they are clean.
你让我失去了一个机会
You just kill my chances.
今晚本应该很美好的
I could have got lucky tonight.
抱歉了
I'm sorry.
谨慎为妙
I have to be careful.
我们再来啊
Let's do it one more time.
很好  继续  来让裙子再飘一点儿
Good, keep on, let your dress flutters.
有了
Got it.
你看  我就说好看吧
See, aren't they great?
我们还有机会
All is not lost.
韩国人?
Korean?
我是中国人
I'm Chinese.
中国人
Chinese!
很漂亮的照片
Beautiful pictures.
你好
Hello...
我是她的经纪人  需要帮忙吗?
I am her agent. Can I help you?
我投资的中东泳装品牌在找模特儿
A middle-eastern swimwear brand I invested in...
靠近他的手机就可以复制手机卡
To copy, just place your phone next to his.
我觉得她非常适合
I think it could be very fit for her.
你可以加我微信
You can add my wechat.
你可以扫我的
You can scan me.
好啊
Sure...
可以了
Got you.
保持联系
I'll be in touch.
夹克不错
Nice jacket.
谢谢
Thanks. Come
怎么样?
how did it go?
复制好了
A copy is made.
美国约翰C·斯坦尼斯号航空母舰
The aircraft carrier USS John c. Stennis
今天抵达拉希德港
arrives today at port rashid
对阿拉伯联台酋长国迪拜
for a four-day visit of Dubai
进行为期四天的访问
in the United Arab Emirates.
现在直播格雷道斯舰长在航母上的讲话
Live from the aircraft carrier, captain Greg dawes.
他们要两亿
They want $200m.
必须现金
It has to be in cash.
我会用黄金支付
I'll pay in gold.
以牙还牙  道斯先生
An eye for an eye, mr dawes!
天气很好
The weather is clear.
只看得见海鸥  没有猎鹰
There are only seagulls, no falcons.
一切安全
It's safe.
我们搞定了警方的监控
We've taken care of the police surveillance.
他们的一切动作皆在掌握
We'll see every move they make.
通知他们交易地点
Tell them the exchange location.
一手交钱一手交货
We pay on delivery.
我爸爸
It's dad!
打开监听设备
Turn on the sound,
监听Marder手机
monitor marder's phone.
长官  交易地点是一个二手车市场
Sir, the location is a second-hand car dealership.
立马派人过去
Send a team there at once.
收到
Yes, sir!
看紧他
Watch him.
目标离开
They are on their way.
这台车多少钱?
How much is this?
两百二十万迪拉姆
About 2.2m dirham.
等于四百万人民币
That's about rmb 4m.
在国内  这款赛道版要一千多万
This special edition costs rmb 10m in China.
那挺划算的
It's a bargain!
给我来一台
I'll take one.
他们到了
Okay, they're coming.
到了
They're here.
通知特警去二手车市场待命
Get SWAT in position.
快点儿
Move it.
黄金在哪儿?
Where's the gold?
老板他们来了
Boss, they're here.
我们终于见面了
Finally we meet.
时间正好
Good timing.
只能看着
Watching from the sideline,
真郁闷
a real bummer!
那可不一定
Not for long...
这里的每一辆黄金车
Each gold car
都价值超过一亿美元
is worth over one hundred million dollars.
车身防弹  车胎防爆
The windows, the tires, are all bullet-proof.
你随便挑两辆吧
You may pick two cars.
多出的算小费
Consider the extra money a gratuity.
我喜欢
I love them!
但是我们怎么把它开出迪拜?
But how do I get them out of Dubai?
这不是问题
It shouldn't be a problem.
这辆车已经被镀箔
This car has foil on it.
黄金镶嵌在下面
It's gold underneath.
镀什么颜色
Choose any colour,
套什么号牌
put a license plate on,
随你喜欢
and you're good to go.
我收下我的礼物
I have my present,
这是你的
here's yours.
简单操作二十公里内击落任何目标
It will take down anything within 20km.
这是我们开发的"雷驰系统
This is called flash mob.
航母停靠在码头
The aircraft carrier is docked
更容易受到攻击
which makes it vulnerable to attack.
它的自动化启动非常快
Its automated system is so fast,
一旦启动
by the time you launch,
对方再反应已经太迟了
it's too late for them to respond.
这就是我们的机器价格不菲的原因
That's why our machine is so expensive.
我要怎么控制?
How do I operate it?
简单
Easy!
像游戏控制器一样
It's like a game controller.
启动
Activate,
点这里锁定目标
lock in the target there,
发射按键
then press launch.
在这里
There.
美军在那次行动
The us army was responsible for the bombing
杀死了Maasym在内  Omar所有的家人
that killed maasym and the rest of Omar's family.
美国约翰C.斯坦尼斯号航母近日在迪拜访问
The USS John c. Stennis is currently in Dubai.
舰长格雷·道斯正是行动的指挥
Captain Greg dawes was the commander of the search and destroy operation.
因此Omar想要报复也就不足为奇了
There is no surprise Omar wants revenge.
立即通知美军
Go tell the us military immediately.
收到
Yes, sir!
你说过会放过我
You said you'd let me go.
我骗你的
I lied.
就正如你骗我父亲
Just like you lied to my father.
我知道你背叛了他
I know you betrayed him,
我保证
and I'm making sure
你会得到应有的后果
you get what you deserve.
震宇先带她去警察总部
Lei, take her to the police hq.
所有单位待命
All units standby!
Fareeda这儿很危险
Fareeda, it's dangerous.
这一路走来
All the way,
从非洲到中东
from Africa to the middle east,
只要有你在我身边
as long as you were by my side,
我都能逢凶化吉
I came through everything unscathed.
所以跟我走
Please come with me.
保护你的安全是我的责任
I have a duty to protect you!
那保护我爸的安全不也是你的责任吗?
Isn't it your duty to protect my father as well?
我不能失去我爸爸
I can't lose my father.
除非你用麻醉枪打晕我
Unless you knock me out with tranquilliser,
不然我是不会跟你走的
I won't go with you.
先生们  这不是演习
Alright, gentlemen, this is not a drill.
现在什么情况?
What's the status?
我们接到了袭击预警
We have a possible hostile attack.
-这里封锁  -请返回
Turn around - go back
-请快离开  -那边
go, go, go - that way
都拿出武器
grab your weapons!
这是我们要救的  人质
This is the hostage we need to save.
走
Move!
我们撤
Let's go!
人质在黄金悍马车上
Hostage's in the gold Hummer.
跟我来
Come with me.
你们都有家伙  我拿什么追啊?
You both have your own gears. What about me?
你不是有这辆车吗?
You've got this truck.
待会儿见
See you later.
站住
Hey! Stop!
不许动
Don't move!
别动
Freeze!
转过身去
Turn around!
手放头上
Hands behind your head!
红色警报  全面戒备
Warning red, weapons tight,
F35战斗机准备起飞
and prepare f35!
探测到的未知机载目标方位角为2-3-2
Unknown airborne object has been detected, 2-3-2,
约16000码
approximately 16,000 yards.
那是什么?
What the hell is that?
我的队员
She's on my team.
我教她的
I teach her.
不许动
Don't move!
神雕
Condor!
你到底有多少个队员?
How many people have you trained?
太多了
Many, many... Go, go, go!
让开
Out of the way!
前进
Move, move!
封锁出口
Secure the exit!
我们又错过什么了?
What have we just missed?
小心
Watch out, watch out!
坐下
Sit down!
往后退
Stay back, stay back.
快出来
C'mon, get up, get up!
不许动
Don't move!
退后  都退后
Back off! I say back off now!
退后
Back off!
都给我趴下  趴下
Get down! I say get down!
都趴下
Get down!
我们需要增援
We need backup.
那边走
- There! - Gol!
待着别动  小心点
- Stay here. - Be careful.
别动  快点
- Stay down! - Move!
快躲起来
Go somewhere safe.
快点
Come on!
等一下
Wait,
那边有楼梯
stairs are over there!
太好了  来
- That's great! - Come, come.
你别动
Stay where you are.
过来
Come
-滚开  -趴下  别动
move - get down! Don't move!
都滚开  快走开
- Get away! - Move!
走开
Move!
走开  出去  走开
- Get off! Get off! - Get away!
走开  滚开
- Move! - Get away!
不许动  都不许动
Don't move. Nobody moves!
都退后  别乱动
Get down, don't move...
别乱动
Nobody...
你干嘛自己打自己?
Why did you shoot yourself?
都别动
Hands up!
举起手
Hands in the air!
Omar在哪里
Where's Omar?
在下面呢
Down there.
-爸爸  -Farccda
- Dad! - Fareeda!
他是怎么下去的?
How did he get down there?
我也不知道
I don't know!
举起手来
Hands up!
放下枪
Drop the gun!
等等  自己人
Wait, he's one of us.
你可以走了
You can go!
谢谢你的配合
Thank you for your cooperation.
谢谢你
Peace be upon you!
没事了
It's all over now.
关于昨天在迪拜发生袭击的最新消息
An update on the attack yesterday in Dubai.
警方已正式报告十五人受伤
The police have officially reported 15 injuries,
没有人员死亡
no casualties.
两架FA-18和一架F35被毁
Two f/a-18 and one f35 were destroyed.
这得力于迪拜警方向美军提供的准确情报
It is all because the Dubai police provided accurate intels to the us military.
所以与此次袭击有关的不法分子
All related to the attack
都已被迪拜警方逮捕
have been arrested by the Dubai police.
此外  警方还截获七辆黄金车
And in addition the police have retrieved seven gold cars
价值超过八亿美元
worth more than 800 million dollars!
晚上好
Good evening!
晚上好  唐先生
Good evening, mr tang.
你好
How are you?
给你介绍一下我的太太
Let me introduce my wife.
Hattawi夫人
Mrs hattawi.
唐焕庭先生  您好
Mr tang, nice to meet you.
你夫人非常…
Your wife is just so...
漂亮
Beautiful.
优雅
Elegant too!
听我先生说
I heard from my husband
这次多亏了你们"急先锋"
that thanks tovanguard
及时提供了关键信息
for their timely and vital info,
才将这次的危机的损失降到了最低
damages were kept to a minimal.
这次的行动
The way that
你先生带领迪拜警察
your husband has led the Dubai police
真是让我大开眼界
was a real eye-opener for us.
你的团队才让我印象深刻
I am the one actually impressed by your amazing team!
这是我们的责任
All in the line of duty!
你们好
Hey, guys,
做得很棒
well done!
-你好  -太感谢"急先锋"了
- How do you do? - Thank you, vanguard
你不是有东西送给人家吗?
don't you have something for her?
老板你怎么知道的?
How did you know, sir?
有什么我不知道的
Nothing escapes me!
去吧
Go on.
走啦
Get out of here!
那…  你送我什么呀?
What have you got for me?
等一下
Wait. Great!
太神奇了
That's amazing!
我的任务完成了
Mission accomplished.
希望你喜欢
Hope you liked it.
很喜欢
Yes, I love it.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢我们干什么啊
Don't thank us,
你得感谢小蜜蜂啊
thank the bees!
看
Look!
中国新年
Chinese new year!
元宵节
Lantern festival!
让我们来一起合个影吧
Let's take a photo together.
来
Sure - come
来吧
come on...
新年好
Happy new year!
恭喜发财
Prosperity and good health to all!
我就像这样…
I was like this...
摩托艇压住了我！
The jet ski pinned me!
我推不上去
I can't push it up,
也不能动
and can't move either.